正如你所看到的那样  接收器本身是很简单的
As you can see, the receiver itself is pretty
就像你在这里看到的  继承BroadcastReceiver这个类
simple. Extend the BroadcastReceiver class and override the
并重写onReceive()方法  接收器是
onReceive handle as you can see here. Receivers are
为了用来监听广播并在5秒内完成相应操作的轻量级组件
lightweight components meant to listen for broadcasts, reacts, and complete
它通常会简单地启动一个服务
within five seconds that usually means simply starting a
或者发送一个通知  要使你的接收器
service or sending a notification. To have your receiver
开始监听广播  你需要注册它
start listening for broadcasts, you need to register it
你可以像这样在你的manifest文件中进行注册
either through an entry in your manifest like this or
或者像这样在另外一个应用程序组件  比如一个Activity中动态的进行注册
dynamically within another application component usually an activity,
然后你需要定义指定了你想接收的
like this. Then you define the intent filter that
广播事件的Intent过滤器
specifies the broadcast event you want to receive.
你可以在manifest文件的这里定义需要过滤的Intent
You can do that either here in the manifest
或者如果你是在一个应用程序组件  例如一个Activity中
or if you're registering your receiver with an
注册的你的广播接收器  你可以像这样
application component such as an activity, you can create
创建你的新的Intent过滤器  在manifest文件中静态注册
your new intent filter like this. The biggest difference
和在代码中动态注册的广播接收器的最大区别就是它们是何时被激活的
between manifest and dynamic receivers is when they're triggered.
一个通过代码动态注册的接收器会仅仅在应用程序运行的时候
A programmatically-registered receiver will only receive broadcasts while
接收广播的消息  而一个在manifest文件中注册的
the app is running. While a manifest declared
接收器将会特地启动你的应用并去接收
receiver will start your app specifically to receive
特定的广播  举个例子
your broadcasts. For example, I usually code with
我经常在戴着我的降噪耳机的时候Coding
my noise cancelling headphones on, so a music
所以一个这样的音乐应用可能需要注册一个
app like this might want to register a runtime
在应用运行时监听系统发出的
receiver to listen to the system intent broadcast
耳机拔出的广播
that announces when headphones are unplugged. That will allow
这将使应用在你的音频从耳机切换到外放时
it to automatically pause playback, when your audio routing switches
自动停止播放  在这种情况下  我们可以使用
from headphone to speakers. In this case, we can use
一个应用运行时的接收器  因为音乐播放的时候
a runtime receiver, because the app is guaranteed to be
应用肯定是处于运行状态的  另一方面
running if music is playing. On the other hand, if I'm
如果我使用Google云消息从我的服务器上监听新的数据
using Google Cloud Messaging to listen for new data from
我想要在manifest文件中注册一个广播接收器  它能一直
my server, I want to register a manifest receiver that always listens
监听服务器传入的数据  并且在应用程序没有运行
for incoming tickles from my server and will wake up
的时候唤醒应用以执行数据更新的代码
my app if it's being terminated to trigger the update code,
通常是一个同步适配器  这是我们将在后面的第六课
usually a sync adapter, which is something we will discuss
要讨论的内容  你可以监听非常多的系统广播
later in lesson six. There's a bunch of system broadcasts
来帮助你的应用程序应对系统的一些变化
you can monitor to help your app react to changes
你可以在developer.android.com网站上的Intent文档部分
in the system. You can see the system broadcast actions within
查看到系统广播对应的Action  广播接收器的一大用途是
the intent documentation at developer.android.com. One great use for broadcast
监听联网状态以及充电状态的变化
receivers is to monitor for changes to internet connectivity or
想象一下你的应用程序需要上传一部电影
charging status. Imagine your app has to upload a movie
或计算象棋游戏中接下来的10,000步
or calculate the next 10,000 moves in a game of chess,
你如何在手机开始这些操作之前使用一个广播接收器监听
how might you use a receiver to wait until the device is plugged in
手机是否被接上电源充电  它应该是一个
before starting that process? Should it be
manifest静态注册的接收器还是一个在代码中动态注册的接收器
a manifest receiver or a broadcast receiver?